Mr friki I have questions I'm just
decorating this portal gate Oh you mean
the doll I left you it's to work out
conflict if you have an issue with me
talk to the doll like it's the real me
but it is not the real you I would just
speak to the real you if we had a
conflict but your heightened emotions
could prevent a productive conversation
I do not experience heightened
emotions and please do not block the
gate with those lights well you told me
this thing doesn't work because the gate
it's attached to in Imperium is not
assembled the portal gate appeared from
out of nowhere caused by mystical
energies we do not yet understand it
could activate at any time well then
whoever arrives will be impressed with
my fancy lighting
Zane we why do you have a frog M
doll it is a long and barely
comprehensible story doesn't matter we
need your help what seems to be the
problem them
[Music]
pH way to shut the portal down I did not
do that perplexing almost as perplexing
as Lord Ross's wolf mask Fighters
chasing you you know who they
[Music]
are wait so this Lord Ros guy took over
Cloud
Kingdom well I don't think he's going to
stop chasing us until he gets bonsel
here we need to find a way to protect
her I agree but it would help us to know
how to protect her if we knew why Ros
wanted her so badly yeah about that I
guess Ros could be after me because of
my secret what secret that I'm not
really a person I'm actually an
extremely powerful ancient spell capable
of banishing ultimate Evil but I've
taken on the form of a physical being
in me I know so much to see together we
will
R
[Music]
we be nin what f
[Applause]
[Music]
nice move there Sora it helps when you
actually built the mech you're fighting
in
[Music]
thanks for the combat demonstration our
evaluation of your basic battle skills
is
complete basic is an understatement
Rising Dragon technique is not just a
set of skills that Rivals shatter spin
it is a guiding principle and cannot be
achieved until one is a third Fang
ninja um we've never heard of a third
Fang ninja or even a first or second
Fang that's because we are the only ones
who award Fang rankings we're going to
break you up into groups based on your
Spinjitsu skills because the motion of
Spinjitsu is the foundation of Rising
Dragon technique I'm the first Fang
teacher Sora rayu you're with me once I
teach you how to do Spinjitsu you'll go
to eal who's the second Fang teacher you
others get over here I'm supposed to try
and teach you Rising Dragon technique
which is probably a waste of my time go
get them Aaron show them how it's done I
know you'll be in our group in no time
Sora you didn't put me in any group ronu
so I guess that means there's like a h
100th Fang level and I'm already there
right you're clearly very talented
Wildfire but your injuries are too fresh
you need to be patient and heal or you
won't be able to ever properly train
again here give that leg
rest you're just leaving me out because
you already have a fire ninja
you think you're a second fire ninja you
realize there's only one master of an
element at a time that's what Lloyd said
but hello explain that Kai is the
elemental master of fire you are the
elemental master of heat fire and heat
go together but are separate
things oh that explains a lot actually
like a lot a lot you didn't even know
your own element
you have much to learn even after your
injury
heals so you're not a person you're a
magical spell yep who took physical form
wait is that how you knew the magic
holding us in the Land of the Lost
things was gone yep spells even ones
that look like flesh and bone or just
bone can sense other spells right before
Raz came it just disappeared why didn't
you tell us any of this before I was
afraid of what you'd think if you knew
about my past it seems the lives of
everyone in the merged Realms are now at
risk you need to tell us the truth
bonsel what's all this I was afraid I'd
have to tell my story one day so I
prepared the best way to do it I rehears
the heck out of
[Music]
this my story starts with the Great
Dragon
Masters the legendary Warriors came to
the most skillful Sorceress in the
magical realm of mysterium because they
needed a spell of intense power they
were about to confront the most
dangerous beings to ever live The
Forbidden five Elemental Masters who
turned to evil and were planning to
conquer all the realms the dragons were
confident they could defeat the five in
battle but they feared no prison would
hold the villains so the Sorceress
worked day and night to weave a spell
that would banish the defeated five to a
place even more permanent than the realm
of The
Departed that spell was me
after the battle was over the Forbidden
five were banished and all the Realms
rejoiced but no one wondered about me
most spells disappear after they're used
the magic all spent but I was a very
strong spell a very complicated spell I
didn't
disappear I even learned how to feel and
what I felt wasn't
good I traveled the realm for centuries
not sure what I was looking for never
losing this terrible unnamed feeling
until one day I met someone who pretty
much changed my life
forever Master
woo remember spin kick and
through good now next
one yes go three for
three strong spin kick game but you need
more elevation lower Bend faster spring
got it I'll get it am I going again nope
ru's
turn uh you sure the the hoop course
doesn't seem uh perfectly suited to ru's
body type I'm sure starting line rayu
time to elevate and
[Music]
dominate remember spin kick and
through reset going again oh uh did no
one tell you that rayu can't fly yet
this exercise has nothing to do with
flying it's to teach your body the
rotational movements used to launch a
Spinjitsu tornado but he can't jump
through those Hoops he's just a dragon
just a dragon the dragons were the first
species of creation no I I didn't sorry
I just mean look at the Hoops those are
way too high for a dragon like him I've
trained many dragons on this course I
even trained on a course like it when I
was his size why dragons can't do
Spinjitsu oh really
[Music]
W yeah I learned Spinjitsu from aasian
cold Fang the wise who learned from the
great king ER leatherwing who had
learned from the first Spinjitsu Master
himself and now you will learn it from
me reset going
again Dragon Ben Jitsu so cool if anyone
ought to be learning from dragons it
should be me I'm basically half dragon
shatter spin is an obsession with
strength strength is important but only
fools believe strength is all important
many things can be more powerful than
strength intelligence Love sometimes
even kindness another
example
motion motion used correctly
can be more powerful than sheer strength
now eliminate all motion be as still as
the
[Music]
mountains how fast are you moving I am
perfectly still
Master
wrong you feel like you're still but in
reality you speed through space the land
on which we stand revolves the entire
world is in motion the universe is
motion but that is all outside of you
except for the movement of the universe
itself are you motionless right now yes
I am Master wrong again the body is
always moving inside the lungs inflate
the brain fires the muscles Buzz with
tension our bodies are motion motion
outside motion inside there is no life
without motion even if the motion is
unseen you must feel it inside you okay
but why because little
fireman only once you connect the motion
of the universe to the motion inside
yourselves can you achieve the Rising
Dragon
technique and that is your only hope of
saving the world from The Forbidden
fives shatter
Spin Master woo never mentioned meeting
a spell like you our meeting probably
wasn't a big deal to him to me it was
[Music]
everything who's
there I'm sorry I'll go
oh excuse my harshness little one you
moved like a
whisper an Unchained
spell H I've heard it was possible but
never expected to see one I never
expected to be one but here I am I've
been wandering the realms for
centuries but you're the first person
who could see me
amazing I'd imagine you have many tales
to tell less than you might think we
spent spent hours talking it was the
first time in my long life that I'd
connected with another living thing he
could even give a name to the bad
feeling I'd had it's called loneliness
and you felt this loneliness before many
times once very terribly what happened I
have a brother and we were very close
going on adventures together making our
way through the Maze of the Sphinx and
facing the Warriors of
felis we were United and bonded sounds
amazing it was but then my brother made
decisions that drove us
apart now we are no longer on the same
side I'm sorry to hear that for a long
time afterward I felt so alone but now I
have students that I teach friends
friends that have become like a family
to me friends can become like family
definitely finding people building
friendships that cured my
loneliness and I bet it would cure
yours who suggested I change myself into
a physical form so I could interact with
others but I had a concern I'm one of
the strongest spells ever woven but to
manifest a physical form would use up a
lot of my strength there are more
important things than strength I took
Master R's
advice I chose a form I felt would suit
me someone who originally felt empty
inside there you are little one how do
you feel I feel like for the first time
ever I've become who I was destined to
be
[Music]
I did it I did it good job Sora rayu
you're
[Music]
up good effort go again rayu oh excuse
me pardon the interruption good peoples
it is is I a completely uninjured mucoid
Warrior coming to partake in the dragon
training I
seeing uh Wildfire what are you doing
Wildfire never heard that name but she's
a great fighter I bet Wildfire we know
it's you no no I'm a
mucoid see marelle you've got the heart
of a winner little Champion but training
before your body is ready ready is worse
than no training at all stupid training
to save the stupid world don't care
about the world anyway it's filled with
[Music]
jerks rayu you did
it
[Music]
yes
go Rising Dragon technique isn't just
about being in motion it's about being
aware of the motion around you moving
around the flow of
[Music]
others watch it me watch it uh you
almost messed up the landing on my stunt
sis this is not about childish stunts
it's about pushing the awareness of
yourselves and your motion out into the
Spinjitsu tornado
itself uh pushing the awareness I I'm
I'm not sure what that means muh I knew
this was a waste of time back to start
adequate
continue sorry I'm dead
W everyone I'm sorry I didn't it's okay
Aaron everyone makes mistakes don't lie
to him that was not
okay because you could achieve a
primitive form of Spinjitsu I thought
you were ready to train in Rising Dragon
but your fundamentals are too raw maybe
you need to go back no wait master I can
pull this together I know I can do you
not realize the fate of the world is at
stake here I I do I won't mess up again
you had better
not the session is over rest now then do
better maybe you and I could do
something
I'm sorry Lloyd I I need to be alone for
a
[Music]
minute so taking Master Woo's advice I
went searching and it was in the land of
lost things where I finally found what I
was looking
for my
family Cole Gio you and the finders
filled that lonely feeling inside me
with a warmth I'd never known
I was afraid if you found out I wasn't a
real person you wouldn't want me to be
in our family
anymore bonsel we don't care where you
came from you're part of our family
nothing's going to change
that I am sorry to interrupt this moment
but I believe I now know why Raz wants
you you are the spell that locked away
the Forbidden five logic would therefore
dictate that you're the spell that could
also free them maybe it would have been
better if I just dissolved after all no
you are loved and needed we'll find a
way to protect you you said you were
created in a place called
mysterium I have never heard of it it's
a magical wonderful place it was one of
the 16 Realms so it must be in the
merged lands now the Sorceress loved it
there then that's it if anyone knows how
to keep you safe it'll be your creator
we have to find her a journey to a land
we have never heard of to find a person
we do not know in the hopes she has a
way of stopping a villainous plan we
only partially understand yeah I know
it's not the best plan but this reminds
me of the old days Count Me In that's
what I'm talking about time for a
[Music]
[Applause]
quest more Force strength is all that
matters and shatters B Cinder
[Music]
Jordana tell me you found the escaped
spell tracking her is not easy once they
went through the portal i
[Music]
w i await your instructions master
Lord RZ I have a new command select five
of the cloud monks they shall be a
sacrifice to the blood moon
[Applause]
[Music]